gameoff.com 2014-05-21

# Privacy Policy - Gameoff

##  We are committed to protect the privacy of our users. This privacy policy explains the type of information we collect directly or for our clients. What information do we collect? 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Appnexus, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Appnexus collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("Non-PII"), including but not limited to an Internet user's IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, the URL, the referring URL, Internet Service Provider, and his or her computer's operating system. Appnexus uses cockies in order to help make the online advertisements you see more relevant to you. 

##  What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

##  Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service. 

##  Opting Out From Cookies 

If you'd like to opt-out from having us or third party collect your Non-PII please [click here](http://ib.adnxs.com/optout). When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your computer. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your Non-PII to help us tailor our Clients' online advertisement campaigns. Please note that if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.. 

##  Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

##  Third party links 

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

##  Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://www.gameoff.com/terms/>. 

##  Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy 

##  Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. <https://www.gameoff.com/en-gb/policy/>.
